Magical Witch Punie- chan
Spin that Princess Rod.
She has descended
from the land of magic.
Spin that magical stick.
Pleased to meet you, Punie Tanaka.
Lightning, sweep, exterminate,
use your powers and rule the world.
Don't trust those kind
words and nice smiles.
Lyrical Tokarev, kill them all.
I will take you to the land of paradise.
There's only one way
to survive, and that is to fight.
There's only one path that leads
to supremacy, and that is by fighting.
We have midterms
starting today. How depressing.
I envy you, Tetsuko.
You're an honors student.
That's not true.
Oh, I can't wait for the exams.
Shall I show you
how much I've studied?
What? You'll show it to
us here, paya? What a waste, paya.
Studied?
Here we go!
2x2. 2x3. 2x4.
4. 6. 8.
2x5. 2x6. 2x7. 2x8.
10. 12. 14. 16.
2x9.
1...
18!
You're amazing!
You mastered this section, paya!
That's like elementary-school level.
They can't go up to sixth level...
That's equivalent to the land of
magic's old-emperor level, paya!
You must be...
...stupid.
No! Don't say that!
Stupid
Episode 5: Can You Decide
Someone's Value with Test Scores?
'm Probably a Zero Anyway.
That's Right.
This is hilarious. The princess
from the land of magic is an idiot.
Will you be okay, Punie-chan?
If you do poorly on these
midterms, you'll repeat the grade.
Don't worry. I've taken care of it.
Ouch!
Class is already in session.
Quiet. Put away everything
but your writing implements.
G-Gesomi!
What happened to Tateno-sensei?
Gesomi?
Tateno-sensei is
absent due to an injury.
Is there a problem
with me being in charge?
This is bad.
If it was that old fart Tateno,
we could've cheated easily...
Hey, what is Gesomi-sensei like?
That's right. You just transferred
here, so you don't know.
She devotes her life
to finding cheaters.
She expelled many in the past.
I'd say she's extremely sadistic!
Don't even think about cheating.
Devoting her life
to such a stupid thing...
Now, begin.
Anego.
What should we do?
At this rate, we'll all repeat the grade.
Anego...
I know!
Don't take your eyes off
Gesomi no matter what.
We can catch her off guard,
even for an instant.
Right.
Now!
Such an old trick...
Isn't there anyone out there?
Cheaters with unique methods
to present a serious challenge.
Get up, you rotten oranges.
I'll give you another chance.
Next time, try to cheat in
a way that will actually excite me.
That is...
...if you have a brain
inside that head of yours.
We're not oranges!
We're human beings!
That's right!
Oh my. You're rotten, but you
can still say nasty things.
What'd you say?
Jeez, Anego-san
gets excited very easily.
What'd you say?
Now's my chance. Come on out.
Understood.
Worry not, Punie-dono.
We studied all night and
mastered the essence of academics.
Those are the veggies from the curry!
Punie-chan's going to let those
manservants do all the cheating.
This is math, Punie-dono?
Right. Hurry up.
Punie-dono, are you aware of this?
What?
We're vegetables given
life by the power of magic.
Temporary puppets.
And so our skills can't be greater
than the one who gave us life.
You can't go beyond my skills?
N-No...
That's right. I am loath
to say this, but this problem...
...is gibberish to me.
What?
I'm sorry.
You're useless.
S-Since it has turned to this,
I will commit hara-kiri!
Potato-dono!
I will atone for my sin by killing myself!
This is for Punie-dono!
Hold it!
Let go!
No, I won't! Death isn't
the only thing for vegetables!
I'm begging you! For pity's sake!
Shut up.
If your suicide could keep me from
being left back, then I needn't suffer.
Is something wrong?
It's nothing.
You people, come
to the detention room later.
Why you... Just wait.
I'm exhausted...
To my loyal vegetables...
This deep situation with the exam,
after looking at my current state...
We must resort to an emergency
measure and keep control of events.
Punie-sama...
The time is 10:20, and this
plan will come to an end.
It's very unfortunate, but we're
going to give up on this exam.
You can return
to being normal vegetables.
Then you'll repeat the grade?
I will not.
Lyrical Tokarev, kill them all!
I can't let them find out the princess
from the land of magic is stupid.
If they were to find out...
I'm going to blow up this planet
and take everyone with me!
That's a Magical A-weapon!
Don't, Punie! If you let that explode...
...it'll turn everything in a radius
of one hundred to smithereens!
You're willing to choose
death over failing an exam?
I haven't teamed up
with you since Vietnam.
Hurry, paya! It's possible
Punie-chan will jump the gun, paya!
Don't worry. No problem.
Leave it to Peter.
That school, right?
George!
Bill! Ronald! Jimmy! Richard!
Abraham!
What? What's going on?
You okay? You're not that hurt!
Hang in there!
Why is it so dark?
Is this the new Tanna Tunnel?
The prototype is passing
Gifu-Hashima Station.
Where do I get off?
Medic! Medic!
This looks bad.
Let's try to get her out of here.
R-Right.
There's a bullet train stationed every
30 minutes at Annakaharuna Station...
Hang on! That's just a delusion!
Hey!
Climb Nitakayama 1208
Tetsuko Koku
Punie Tanaka
Tora! Tora! Tora!
Good job, paya! Let's flee, paya!
Aye aye, sir!
That was close, paya.
It was about to turn ugly, paya.
Payatan.
What is it, paya?
Can you come back to
the squad, Colonel Paya Livingston?
Squad?
The squad, huh?
Let's not talk about that.
I'm just a magical girl's mascot now.
Colonel...
Sorry about that!
Forget it!
Okay, paya! I'll forget, paya!
What was that?
Don't tell me someone
used the army to cheat...
Oh my.
That's it, folks!
Pass up your papers from the back.
Who could take a test this way!
Something's wrong with you, Gesomi!
Yeah! Yeah!
That's too bad...
Even though you're stupid,
I'll still be your friend.
It was Punie, all right.
She got a zero...
...but she didn't get left back
due to good overall marks.
Happy ending indeed.
Good morning, Anego-san.
We've met every morning lately.
Y-Yeah, that's true.
We'll be late if we don't hurry. Later.
Hey, Yamada...
What the hell.
I can't believe a person like me...
...would fall in love.
But falling in love isn't my thing.
If they found out,
I wonder what everyone would say.
I have to make sure
no one finds out...
I found a great toy.
Paya.
Episode 6: When I Saw You Sweep
Back Your Bangs Under the Apple Tree
with the Flower-comb in Your Hair,
I Thought You Were a Flower Too...
Hey, confessed to Yamada yet?
Come here!
You didn't tell anyone, did you?
Of course not.
You have strong feelings for him.
Why would I go tell others about it?
Do you know?
What?
About Anego-san and Yamada-kun...
Can't help that it's out.
That's right. I'm in love.
That's wonderful!
But it won't work.
I've already given up.
Why?
I'm the leader
who's in control of this area.
But compared to me,
he was brought up sheltered.
He has a good personality,
and everyone loves him.
We're like night and day. It won't work.
Oh, but those are the types of
people that tend to be insidious.
A brute and a hussy.
You'll make a great couple.
Don't base things on your values!
Anyway, I decided not to get
too deep. Leave me alone.
That's really okay?
You're annoying.
Feeling nervous when confessing...
Feeling excited waiting for the reply...
But when they turn you down,
you become very sad.
I think those are special
privileges that only girls have.
Punie...
Here, take this.
I'm sorry about before.
Punie-chan is right.
You can have this. I won this from
Monthly Railroad Fan magazine.
Amusement park tickets!
That's right.
You should ask if he wants to go.
Well, but...
Come on!
Go! Go!
Hey, Anego-san. What is it?
Oh, well...
Um, do you have
any plans this weekend?
No, I'm free. Why?
I understand if you don't want to...
...but I got these tickets
for an amusement park.
Would you like to go with me?
Sure.
Really?
I've been wanting
to go there for a while.
My good friends!
You did it, Anego-san!
I'm sorry about
before, Punie, Tetsuko.
Have a great time.
He's running late.
Yeah.
I can hear Punie's voice!
Huh? Something's in my ear.
We'll advise you
from behind the scenes.
Good luck, Anego-san!
I don't need your help!
Oh? Who do you think
made this date possible?
Hey, here he comes.
Left! Left!
Sorry about that!
Sorry I'm late. Wait long?
No, not at all.
She said she didn't wait.
She came an hour early too.
I'll kill them...
I'll kill them later for sure...
Mouse Land
What should we ride first?
Let's see...
How about the roller coaster?
Good idea.
Go and tell him. Say you
want to ride the roller coaster.
Come on!
I have no say in this?
If they enjoy plenty of thrills, their bond
will become stronger than ever.
Really?
But somehow,
this doesn't look thrilling at all...
I know!
Lyrical Tokarev, kill them all!
Spirits, provide
more thrills for Anego-san!
I'm really scared of things like this.
I'm perfectly fine.
I'm not scared at all...
This kind of feels too high...
I was a fool.
I should've never listened to her.
This is a strange amusement park.
Hey, should we go there now?
We're going already?
I'm begging you, Punie.
Leave us alone...
What are you saying?
The real fun begins here.
You're on an amusement-park
date, so you have to go there.
Mansion of Fear
Wow, a mansion of fear.
Sounds good.
Holding each other out of fear
of the dark... And while they're at it...
What are you trying
to make me say, Punie-chan?
Oh, stop it!
I prepared the greatest terror of all.
I'll make you regret ever being born.
If it's man-made, it's not scary at all...
...but if it's Punie,
who knows what could happen?
This is bad. I want to go home...
Are you trembling?
N-No way!
Don't worry. I'm here by your side.
Let's go!
I-I-I'm holding hands with him!
Thank you, Punie!
It's so dark that I can't see anything.
I'm kind of nervous.
The highway?
Anego-san, how do
you like the mansion of fear?
I don't know...
The bloodcurdling
terror I prepared for you...
It's a drive on the metropolitan
highway, and the driver is...
...a car-manga-influenced, newly
licensed idiot who thinks he can drive!
Don't worry! Really!
I'm really dangerous!
I'm really good at driving!
Idiot! Eyes on the road!
They are!
I'll never get into an accident!
You're annoying!
Yeah! This is such a great feeling!
I'll do the counter!
Wow, I'm drifting! This can't be real!
You're spinning, idiot!
I'm not an idiot! I'm really smart!
I can get into Tokyo University!
Punie Tanaka's Store
(For Personal Use)
Great Magic Ridge
This is great! It's really great!
This is better than mugging people!
Should I drift again?
Okay!
This is great!
I'm a genius! A super genius!
Where do I shift up?
No, that's reverse. I'm not even
stepping on the clutch. This is a hoot.
Are you okay, Yamada-kun?
I don't want to go on
dates anymore! Mama!
It's over.
My first love...
And what happened to
Anego-san afterwards...
What are you looking at?
She's gotten
even worse than before...
You'll be unattractive.
Shut up!
If you bend the knees upside down...
...even your belief about
crushing a rock becomes distorted.
Good, justice, and even the truth
is gone when you feel the pain.
Even those with fortitude have joints.
Take a look. This is
the submission of a monarch.
As long as you
have fortitude, you will prosper.
Next, "Don't Think Participation
Is Important. That's Too Lenient."
"We Can't Just
Stay the Way We Are."
"It's Kind of Scary
Becoming an Adult."
Choo-choo!