Punie's Homecoming:
State of the Society
So we're here in the land of magic!
Like its name suggests, this place is
filled with buildings out of fairy tales.
It's wonderful, right?
I'm jealous. I'd like
to live somewhere fun like...
Get him!
Punie-chan...
What is this place?
You can't do much
about economic inequality.
It can't be helped. If we don't exploit
them, the country can't stand.
Weird.
It normally passes right
through this area. Is it terrorism?
Terrorism?
Divine punishment!
Why do you treat your people like this?
We'll be taking your life!
As I thought, terrorists.
I can't avoid this.
I'll take care of them with my magic.
They're so poor,
yet they have Anisakis shields!
With those around, my magical
attacks will be rendered useless.
My magic won't work, so...
I'll have to use submission holds!
Princess Manji Hold!
Princess Standing Neck Lock!
Princess Telephone Arm Lock!
Rioting over a little
oppression is uncalled for.
Say, is the land of magic
a dictatorship devastated by fascism?
We're almost at
the royal palace. Let's head on out!
I'm Punie, a magical princess.
The reason I came to
the world of humans is a secret.