Punie, listen to me very carefully.
Yes, Mama.
Starting today, you're going
to spend a year living on Earth.
I'm sure there will be many
difficult tasks ahead for you.
But you must find a way
to overcome those things. Because...
If you get lonely,
you can always come back...
No need to say
such unnecessary things.
Oh, but I'm fine.
I mean, this is a test
to become the next queen!
Now, that's my daughter.
Punie!
I'm going now, Papa, Mama.
Go!
I'm Punie Tanaka, a transfer from
Saint Magic Academy up in the sky!
Nice to meet you!
Anego.
I don't like it.
Seducing men like
that and being conceited.
That's the type I hate the most.
Should we teach her a good lesson?
Ashtray.
Mind your own business.
I'll do it myself!
Hey, you need to keep it quiet.
Shut up!
Ouch...
Why?
Magical Witch Punie- chan
Spin that Princess Rod.
She has descended
from the land of magic.
Spin that magical stick.
Pleased to meet you, Punie Tanaka.
Lightning, sweep, exterminate,
use your powers and rule the world.
Don't trust those kind
words and nice smiles.
Lyrical Tokarev, kill them all.
I will take you to the land of paradise.
There's only one way
to survive, and that is to fight.
There's only one path that leads
to supremacy, and that is by fighting.
Episode 1: Miracle Rod Causes
a Huge Panic at the School Festival!?
Magical Princess
Punie- chan Appears!!
Wow!
What a perfectly clear sky!
Earth is such a really clean place!
I really like this place!
So cute...
She's so innocent.
These beautiful
forests, land, and skies.
When I become
the queen, they'll all be mine!
Hey, what are you
grinning about? You disgust me.
Making eye contact with
the guys and getting their attention.
You must be very pleased, miss.
Oh, that was a charm spell.
Every girl has it.
You're very pretty, so you can
probably use a wonderful charm.
Why you...
You wanna fight?
Lyrical Tokarev, kill them all!
Powers of the earth,
please protect me!
What are they?
Stop picking on Punie-chan!
Take that!
Anego, they're pretty tasty.
I'm still raw!
Don't get carried away
just because you can use magic!
Carrot! Potato!
Cabbage! Cucumber! Onion!
Garlic! Melon! Eggplant! Pumpkin!
Corn! Burdock! Chinese cabbage!
Sakurajima radish! Broccoli!
Goya! Japanese yam!
Life expectancy
for humans is 50 years
Wow! Amazing!
Yes!
It's like they're welcoming
you with their blessings.
110th School Festival
So, this is the school festival.
So many stands!
I came at a really perfect time.
Earth has such interesting customs.
If I become queen, maybe
I'll establish a magic school here.
What the hell is this?
You people trying to kill us?
Everyone, their curry
has cockroaches in it!
I can't eat this stuff, you idiot!
What? We try hard to make
our food sanitary. This can't be...
There must be
some misunderstanding!
This was in your curry!
All right, trash this place!
Yeah!
What'll you trash?
You know. We'll turn
this place upside down...
You...
Well, you see...
Let's go!
Right.
I don't know who you are,
but thank you very much!
What happened?
Railroad Research Committee's
Famous Curry- It's delicious!
For some reason,
that group targets and harasses me.
As a result, no one buys from us.
I'm sorry to hear that.
I'll be your customer.
Can I have an order of curry?
We have an order! One curry please!
Coming!
Thanks for waiting.
Wow, looks delicious! Bon appétit!
Turmeric, cumin seed, chili powder,
cardamom, clove, and others.
Curry is filled with lots of spices.
How is the taste, miss?
Get me the store owner.
This isn't curry.
It's yellow feed.
So mean!
The temperature, quality, and spices'
scent... Aren't they the same as ever?
If you made it according
to recipe, it's just ridiculous.
It's a typical, awful curry
made by an amateur.
Hey, hey, hey!
Boss!
Lyrical Tokarev, kill them all!
You don't have to depend
on popular spices.
You love the railroad, so there's
a curry only you can make.
A curry that only I can make?
I know. I can use that method.
Boss, it'll work if it's that.
You're right.
Let's do a good job, everyone.
Yeah!
But I wonder why Anego and
her gang want to harass her?
Maiden Curry Hall
We don't have any customers.
Should I go fetch a few?
Why don't you try some curry?
It's really good though.
Does this mean...
...that we're not maidens?
What are you saying?
You're one fine maiden!
You made such good curry.
Damn... If it wasn't
for that magical pendant...
I see. So that magical
pendant is getting in your way?
Who're you?
If you're in here,
you better order something.
What if I told you this statue of the evil
god Anisakis could inhibit her magic?
If she had no magic,
we wouldn't be afraid of her.
We'd give her a beating and send
her back to the land of magic.
Is that right? Then I shall give you this.
Okay.
Bad news!
The railroad-research curry is...
Give me some curry!
Hurry!
What's going on?
This seems like ordinary curry,
but what is this strange nostalgia?
This container isn't an ordinary one...
Seven hundred... Three hundred...
This is...
The old bullet train!
Yes, this is the long-lost flavor
of the bullet train buffet curry!
But this isn't just a recreation!
The stars are these vegetables!
How fresh and juicy!
These vegetables are alive!
The vegetables are alive?
Not good. Where are they making it?
The home ec room. What'll you do?
You know! Did you forget
how I take care of things?
Can we become delicious curry?
Well, let's go!
Yeah!
What's wrong?
I'm kind of afraid to jump in...
Shameful... Bring me the peeler!
Yes, sir!
Isn't this the time to repay
Punie-sama for her great gratitude?
Why should you hesitate?
He's peeling his own skin!
Carrot-dono, I'm sorry,
but where is the pot?
You can't see?
Carrot-dono, we veggies
have to show mercy.
Sorry!
See you later.
Potato-dono!
We'll be joining you shortly!
The vegetables really are alive.
She's a witch after all...
I'll destroy them. This curry is evil!
Please don't do that.
Punie!
I'll have to use a punishment
spell on people like you.
Lyrical Tokarev, kill them all!
Take this!
That's a statue of Anisakis!
Where'd you get that?
That's none of your business.
I suppressed your magic now.
Gang, beat her up!
Yeah!
What should I do?
I can't use my Princess Rod.
Then...
I'll give you some pain!
Then I'll have to respond
by getting physical!
Die!
Princess Arm Lock!
You little bitch!
Princess Choke Sleeper!
Princess Foot Lock!
Princess Americana!
Princess Guillotine Choke Sleeper!
W-What's with those simple
but painful-looking moves?
Striking...
Striking is unnecessary in a fight.
Effective
A champion uses submission holds.
Princess...
No! I don't like painful ones!
...Achilles Hold!
Oops, I did it again.
I knew a girl gang leader couldn't do it.
Stopping the trials is hard.
Oh, what's wrong?
We can't sell any of our baked squid.
I'm sorry!
Leave it to me. I'll give you
the best baked squid in the world.
Lyrical Tokarev, kill them all!
It's a monster squid!
My son's still in the building!
Help me!
Boss!
Oops.
No, I'll be late. Watching "Goodbye,
Blue Train Morning Breeze, Sakura"...
...on DVD so late was a mistake.
Excuse me...
Sorry, I'm in a rush!
Do you have anything to eat?
Oh no! Take my special
"assorted bento from the peak."
Wow!
Delicious, paya!
Thank you, paya.
I don't know how to thank you.
You're welcome.
Pa
I'm Payatan.
I'm from the land of magic.
Magic?
Right, paya.
I came to find my master, paya.
Good morning, Tetsuko-chan!
Good morning.
P-P-Punie-sama!
Payatan!
Punie-sama!
Why did you leave without saying
a word? Don't you like me anymore?
It's not like that, Payatan.
It was hard to say goodbye,
so I left without a word.
Punie-sama!
Payatan!
Episode 2: Playful and
Cute Mascot Payatan Appears!!
So a mascot always stays with
the witch in the land of magic?
Right, paya.
But you shouldn't have
followed me when I'm in training.
Mama might get mad at you.
It's fine, paya.
I want to be with you even so.
Jeez.
You two get along very well.
I want a mascot like Payatan too.
You should go to Exciting Mascot
Village. Many of my friends are there.
"Exciting Mascot Village"?
Sounds like fun!
I still remember when I went to see
Payatan at Exciting Mascot Village.
Paya.
Exciting Mascot Village
Go away!
You're obstructing my business!
There! All right, 4, 5, 6!
And this broad was really something.
Who the hell are you?
I came to get a mascot.
A mascot! I didn't know
dumb witches were around!
There's no one here
that you can handle.
Did you mix this up with
the south's "Cheery Mascot Village"?
This place is only full of guys like us!
Ow, ow, ow...
Don't get me wrong.
My business isn't with you lowlives.
Let go! You'll break my arm!
If you don't let go,
you'll be in big trouble!
I broke it.
Now, what kind of trouble am I in?
You bitch!
Stop it.
You're no match for her.
Bro...
Bro Payatan...
Move.
You're Payatan? Your fame
has reached our kingdom as well.
Booze
Bartender, get me the usual.
Got it.
Coffee Milk
Listen, miss.
This is a place to drink and have fun.
If you have eyes as shiny as a sword,
you won't live very long in this village.
You should get out of this village
and confine yourself in some city.
It's for the best, but I guess
you didn't come here to talk after all.
Step outside.
Be my mascot, Payatan.
You'll have a successful future.
I'm not really good at serving people.
Well, grumbling about
this and that won't do anything.
If you want to make me your mascot,
defeat me. That's the rule.
Fine!
Princess Kneebar!
Paya.
Princess V1 Armlock!
Princess Camel Clutch!
Paya.
Sorry, but my body is rather unique.
Every joint moves 360 degrees,
so submission holds won't work.
Somebody, contact her kingdom.
She won't be able to move
on her own for a while.
Don't think it's over yet.
I really like you now.
You'll make a perfect servant.
You're gonna die, miss.
Defeat is the same
as death in the royal family.
Princess Headlock!
Jeez, I thought you'd use some
amazing move, but a headlock?
It's nothing special,
and I'm disappointed.
A headlock is nothing
special? You're so naive.
What?
No way! He's in pain!
Impossible!
His head can smash huge rocks!
You should do your homework.
The skull has a juncture.
Which means it has a joint.
Headlocks use that to directly attack
the brain, a deadly submission hold.
It feels like someone's
grabbing my brain...
A champion uses submission holds.
There are no holds
that I can't master!
He's been beaten!
Let's flee!
Now, keep your promise.
Be my mascot.
You'll regret it...
When you sleep... When you eat...
I can promise you that
you'll never feel safe again!
I'm definitely going to kill you!
What's so funny?
If I can't handle one or two
servants who are after my life...
...how can I call myself royalty?
You're a strange princess.
Take out your mascot contract.
This life that I have...
I swear to serve you as long as I live.
We've been friends ever since, right?
Right?
Let's go to school!
Let's go, paya!
Let's go!
Go, paya!
They've gone through a lot,
but they get along now, so...
What's wrong, Tetsuko-chan?
What is it, paya?
It's nothing!
He's after her!
He's still itching to kill her!
We're going to be late! Let's hurry!
Paya!
I didn't use any magic this time, did I?
You don't need any magic.
Oh, Anego-san. You're alive?
I'm not dead yet!
Hehe.
To Be Continued
If you bend the knees upside down...
...even your belief about
crushing a rock becomes distorted.
Good, justice, and even the truth
is gone when you feel the pain.
Even those with fortitude have joints.
Take a look. This is
the submission of a monarch.
As long as you
have fortitude, you will prosper.
Next Magical Witch Punie-chan,
"Shocking Breakfast Strategy?"
"If a Little Cuckoo
Doesn't Chirp, Kill It!"
"Oh, So Cute! Did You Know the
Chances of Having Twins Are 1l120?"
Please look forward to it!