Magical Witch Punie-chan
Spin that Princess Rod.
She has descended
from the land of magic.
Spin that magical stick.
Pleased to meet you, Punie Tanaka.
Lightning, sweep, exterminate,
use your powers and rule the world.
Don’t trust those kind
words and nice smiles.
Lyrical Tokarev, kill them all.
I will take you to the land of paradise.
There’s only one way
to survive, and that is to fight.
There’s only one path that leads
to supremacy, and that is by fighting.
Railroad Journal
Handmade Noodles
Suspicious empire
Rise and revolt!
Overthrow the traitor!
If you bend the knees upside down…
…even your belief about
crushing a rock becomes distorted.
Good, justice, and even the truth
is gone when you feel the pain.
Even those with fortitude have joints.
Take a look. This is
the submission of a monarch.
As long as you
have fortitude, you will prosper.