Magical Witch Punie-chan
Spin that Princess Rod.
She has descended
from the land of magic.
Spin that magical stick.
Pleased to meet you, Punie Tanaka.
Lightning, sweep, exterminate,
use your powers and rule the world.
Don’t trust those kind
words and nice smiles.
Lyrical Tokarev, kill them all.
I will take you to the land of paradise.
There’s only one way
to survive, and that is to fight.
There’s only one path that leads
to supremacy, and that is by fighting.
Why, Punie Tanaka-kun?
Principal…
My time here on Earth is almost up.
While I’m here, I want to make
as many fun memories as I can…
You want to be on the sports
festival’s executive committee?
I’m sorry if I sound too selfish…
I can’t, right?
No problem!
Go and do your best!
Episode 7: Don’t Think Participation
Is Important. That’s Too Lenient.
Sports Festival
White Team
Red Team
The girls’ spoon race will start soon.
Participants, head to the gate now.
What’s the matter, Anego-san?
Hurry up and go to the gate.
Look at the executive committee.
The witch is smiling with
a perfectly straight face.
What?
You didn’t know?
Every event for today’s sports
festival is being produced by Punie.
This year’s sports festival
is gonna get a little ugly.
Coming up is
the second-year girls’ spoon race.
On your mark, paya.
Ready…
Bang!
Wow! Anego-san is really fast!
She’s in first place!
She’s far ahead of the others!
This is too easy…
These are eggs prepared by Punie.
It’s possible. With her, anything is.
Excuse me.
Freight train is connected.
Ready to go!
Hey!
Choo-choo! Choo-choo!
Don’t, Tetsuko! That egg…
The red team’s
Tetsuko Koku is in first place!
I did it!
Maybe you’re just
thinking too much, Anego.
A regular egg?
Executive Committee Member
H-Her eyes are so calm.
Don’t tell me she’ll do
this sports festival fair and square.
Go! Go! Red team!
Big Sister!
Pyun, Potaru, what is it?
We made some lunch.
Let’s eat.
Wow! Thank you.
Yay! Yay!
You delinquent women,
there’s enough for you too.
You should be grateful, pig.
Thanks…
Bon appétit!
Wow! This is amazing!
They look good…
Aren’t you going to eat?
Looks like they’re not poisoned.
I’m a taste tester?
Hey, Big Sister!
We want to be
in the sports festival too!
Sure, that’s fine.
You’re sure?
It’s dangerous for small kids.
It’s my first time experiencing
something this wonderful.
I want to let them participate as well.
Trying to be a goody-goody…
You’re planning to win
at the end with magic, right?
After becoming
an executive committee member…
…and researching
the sports festival, I understood.
There are many wonderful
cultures here on Earth.
I was about to head home
to the land of magic…
…without experiencing any of them.
Punie…
Anego-san.
The mock cavalry battle at the end…
Will you compete earnestly with me?
I won’t use magic.
I’ll compete fair and square.
I want to have
good memories with you.
I’m going to take
that bandana off your head.
I won’t lose.
The mock cavalry battle starts now.
Victory for White Team
White Team
Red Team
Goodness, the teams are tied.
Here comes the red team!
And now, here comes the white team!
Come on, Puni…
What?
Punie
Punie Cavalry!
The White Rose Squad is here!
You brought a real cavalry?
This is your first battle.
Look well at how your sister fights.
Yes, Big Sister!
Shout for victory!
Charge!
Anego, here they come!
Damn! Pull back! Retreat!
Come on, come on, come on!
I got him!
I-I did it, master!
Well done on the first strike.
A Godiva truffle!
I’m expecting you to do more.
Go and get more.
Respond with more action.
Yes, ma’am!
With great physical strength!
One after another, our army
is taking down the enemy.
Victory is only a matter of time.
So…
I see.
Huh? What’s she doing?
She’s definitely off guard.
Time to strike.
Punie
Pyun & Potaru
Start the horses!
Our enemies are on the athletic field!
Take the old traitor’s head!
Great God!
Help us defeat our enemy!
Who the hell?
What?
T-They attacked our weak flank…
What? What about the reserves?
Pyun-dono and Potaru-dono
are rebelling against us!
Our army is getting defeated!
Stop fussing!
Master!
Damn you…
You backstabbed your sister!
First and second troops, flank right!
Join the third troop
and create a circle formation!
Attack both sides!
You delinquent woman,
you should give yourself up.
What? Punie’s army
seems to be in disarray.
Guys, now!
Don’t think you’re better than us…
…just because you’re on a horse!
Why you!
That’s dangerous!
How many allies survived?
It is only you and myself, master.
There’s no escape for you now.
You used such a dirty trick…
Get ready.
Paya!
Payatan!
Please flee!
Let me handle this!
I’ll see you again
at the river of the dead!
Payatan! Payatan!
I’m sorry, Payatan… It’s all my fault…
After her! Don’t let the witch escape!
I guess the era of
close combat has already ended…
From now on…
…it’s the era of guns.
Muskets!
Fire!
Next!
Afterwards, this battle…
…became known as the first time
guns were used in battle in Japan.
It marked its place in
the history of sports festivals.
This was already
a major event anyway…
Take that! Take that!
Bad girls!
I baked the cupcakes, Potaru.
Looks delicious!
I made it to this recipe,
but I wonder if I did it right.
Bon appétit!
Wow!
Delicious.
Here it comes!
It worked, Potaru.
We’ll get Big Sister with this…
Episode 8:
We Can’t Just Stay the Way We Are.
It’s Kind of Scary
Becoming an Adult.
Good morning,
Anego-san, Tetsuko-chan!
Paya!
Yo.
Morning, Punie-chan.
It’s another lovely day.
Huh? What’s going on?
Gorgeous.
I can’t control myself anymore!
They’re pretty.
Are they celebrities?
Maybe a photo shoot?
I’m jealous. I wish I were like them.
Don’t worry, Tetsuko-chan. You have
boobs that are like a super bullet train.
You think?
Let’s go. We’ll be late.
Oh, so you’ll just pass right by us?
Big Sister…
Big Sister?
Don’t tell me you two…
…are Pyun and Potaru?
How did you become adults?
We saw the “Book of the Dead”
on a Yahoo auction.
And that book had
an arcana of growth.
Big Sister… No, turd-Punie…
Do you know why
we couldn’t beat you?
Oh? I wonder what’s wrong?
She’s shaking like an innocent girl.
She knows.
The reason why
we couldn’t beat this delinquent…
…is that we were little!
Princess Gemini Monkey Flip!
Punie-chan!
Punie!
Gemini Knee Drop!
Gemini Drop Kick!
Gemini Pile Driver!
Gemini Hell Strike!
Gemini…
…Guillotine!
They’re strong!
Their magical and
physical power is greater.
They’re undoubtedly
the strongest foes.
This is bad! This is bad!
My lovely daughters
are killing each other!
Ouch! My stomach…
Darling.
Do you know why I was
able to become the queen?
Because you’re the strongest
witch in the land of magic.
Not at all.
There were many witches
whom were stronger than me.
Akko, Sally, Meg…
And Momo.
The reason I was
able to become queen…
…is that I kept beating those
whom were stronger than me.
In order to become the queen, you
need strength plus something else.
This is bad…
I don’t think I can win…
We’ll forget what you
did to us, rotten punk.
We won’t take time
beating you to death.
We’ll kill you quickly, ugly bitch.
Listen to yourselves…
I can’t believe
you’re showing me mercy…
With your powers, you can
kill me and Queen Esmeralda…
…and have the land of magic
in the palms of your hands.
But after that…
…which one will be the queen?
Only one can.
It doesn’t matter!
Only one of us
will profit from this, Potaru.
You can kill me and Pyun
at the same time now, Potaru.
What’s wrong, Pyun?
Nothing…
She did it.
She’s a scary individual, as usual.
How so?
The twin attacks…
Which part do you think
is most problematic?
The high-spirited combo play.
But look now.
With a word or two, she placed
doubt into the twins’ minds.
Now they can’t use combo play.
Crafty!
Unprincesslike craftiness.
Could she be the true witch?
Payatan?
Interesting.
You’re definitely interesting.
I, Payatan, will follow
you to the depths of hell.
Don’t be overwhelmed.
Submission holds
are meant for one-on-one combat.
That choke sleeper
before proved it, right?
That certainly is the greatest
weakness of submission holds.
But I’ve been practicing how to fight
one on two for the last eight years.
Eight years ago?
Wait a minute!
We’re only eight years old!
That means…
When we were born into this world…
You were ready to fight both of us?
That’s right.
I came up with this technique
in order to fight you twins.
In other words, it’s sisterly love.
Accept your sister’s love!
Princess…
No!
…Spinning Toe Hold!
The finish.
Princess Forty-four Magnum!
We were wrong! We should’ve…
…never made her our enemy!
Huh?
The arcana’s effects wore off.
I won’t forgive you
just because it wore off.
Big Sister…
Your punishment is just beginning.
Punie-chan, please forgive them!
I won’t forgive you!
Tickle, tickle, tickle!
Punie-chan…
Looks like the land of magic
will be peaceful for a while…
The End
If you bend the knees upside down…
…even your belief about
crushing a rock becomes distorted.
Good, justice, and even the truth
is gone when you feel the pain.
Even those with fortitude have joints.
Take a look. This is
the submission of a monarch.
As long as you
have fortitude, you will prosper.